(The Reason Behind Happiness)
- It's nice to see you, everyone. - Nice to see you.
My dear Sung Hwan, have you been well?
- I've been well. - Gosh.
Here's the thing. He hasn't been near our show...
after losing the race to me last time. I guess he was upset.
(He challenged Sung Hwan to a running race all of a sudden.)
Go!
(The race took place in the middle of the night.)
(In the end, Moomoo won the race.)
(I have a cramp in my leg.)
(Sung Hwan was only left with an excuse.)
Well, I did get a cramp in my leg. That's the truth.
- So you lost. - Yes.
- Yes, I lost. - You were so bad at running.
I lost. I know.
- I lost. - I thought you'd be good.
- No. - He was the worst.
Listen. During the race,
I tried to sprint at first. I have good upper body strength.
- He had good upper body strength? - So when I was running,
I got a cramp in my leg.
Despite that, I ran 20m more...
purely based on my mental strength. That's how we were tied.
- I see. - Oh, my.
Is it necessary to review the race in such detail?
The thing is...
(Chuckling)
It's like he's being chased.
- His glasses are steaming up. - Right.
- No. They aren't steaming up. - Are you already hot?
- This is... - Are you crying, Sung Hwan?
They're getting misty.
You know what? Let's do it again...
- once my leg cramp is gone. - Let's do it now.
- When will that happen exactly? - Let's do it whenever.
Then let's hold a sports day.
We can make your race the main event of the sports day.
But making that the main event sounds ridiculous.
- This is the main event? - Right?
Since we're on the subject, you and I...
- should have a go at it. - Then let's do this.
- Do what? - We'll divide into...
- Team Sung Hwan and Team Hyun Moo. - Okay.
Team Moo and Team Ku.
I'll join Team Hyun Moo then.
- Same here. - Me too.
(Team Moo, not Team Ku?)
Hold on.
Who knew I'd be their first pick?
- Hold on. - I want to be on Team Hyun Moo.
- Me too. - Okay.
Okay. Let's do this then.
- I'll prepare myself for it. - Gosh, challenge me whenever.
Sure. I've got nothing to worry about.
- You know what? Something crazy... - Yes.
Happened during the weekend.
I'm serious when I say this.
He's one of my cherished stars I hold dear to my heart.
You mean SAN?
(Na Rae has recently been hooked on...)
(the K-pop group, ATEEZ.)
(And her favorite star is SAN.)
(I want my sweethearts to be happy.)
(A few days later, on Hyun Moo's social media)
- Gosh. - Hello.
- Hong Joong. - Hello.
- SAN. - Hello.
(The greeting from the man Na Rae is into)
(What is this? What? He's my favorite!)
(Na Rae was furious after watching the clip.)
- You have never... - Right.
Mentioned ATEEZ or even so much as their music.
- Why did you go there? - Right.
He posted the clip almost right away.
That's the only hobby I have. Why did you have to take it from me?
But SAN is mine.
What...
Na Rae, I'll sing their song at karaoke.
No!
How about Kian84 instead of SAN?
(He will perform for only one person.)
I'll sing their song.
Anyway, I brought something from Japan.
- What? - What?
- He must've brought a present. - He must've brought a souvenir.
My gosh. I knew you'd be furious.
So I got you a present despite my busy schedule.
- What is it? - You know? Here.
This is their merchandise shirt. It's the same design SAN wore.
It's ATEEZ's shirt. I got him to sign the shirt.
- My gosh. Really? - Here.
- Thank you. - Exactly.
- Thank you. - You can't even find this online...
- because the design is sold out. - Yes.
- Check the back. - Hold on.
(Carefully checking the shirt not to damage it)
- Let's see. - Gosh. Are you that happy?
- Hold on. There it is. - It's there.
There it is.
- "To Na Rae. - "Na Rae."
"Na Rae, I'm always grateful."
- "Have a good day." - Yes.
- Gosh. - I'll forever be loyal to you.
- You're not upset now. Right? - Yes.
- I went there to get you this. - I'm sorry.
- He's indeed Fathermoo. - For you,
I'd give up a kidney.
(Feeling proud)
(More Joy in Being Together)
The weather is great.
(Going somewhere with a bag, full of bread)
(It's Ju Seung.)
(In a good mood)
(I've arrived!)
All right.
(He naturally grabs the package.)
- Isn't that his mother's house? - Right. Isn't that his mom's house?
My goodness.
(Opening up)
Come back in, Coco.
- Come in. Yes. - It's Coco.
(Ju Seung visits his mother's house and is welcomed by Coco.)
- We've gotten close. - Yes, you have.
- She's wagging her tail. - Is Ju Seung here?
Who is it? Is it your brother or sister?
- Come on in. - It's your brother. Come on in.
Come in.
- You've gotten very close. - Yes.
(Happy to see Coco)
- You got a package. - Put it there.
- That's your brother. - It's your brother.
Is it from the online shopping mall?
(He runs a restaurant in Vietnam.)
(Ju Seung's brother, Ju Ang)
- Where's my sister-in-law? - Give it to me.
Your sister-in-law?
- Did she come with him? - I bought some bread.
- It was supposed to come yesterday. - Bread?
- Bread... Hello. - Hello, Ju Seung.
- My gosh. - What?
- My gosh. - I see.
- That's your sister-in-law. - Hello, Ju Seung.
- She's so beautiful. - Oh, my.
Why did you buy so much bread?
A new bakery opened up in the neighborhood.
Gosh, it tastes great.
It tastes great?
(There's a wide array of tasty bread.)
- She's not fluent in Korean yet. - Right.
My sister-in-law's name is...
Nguyen Thi Minh Thu. That's her name.
They had their wedding...
in Vietnam last September.
After being married for a year,
they had their second wedding in Korea.
- The wedding was a week ago. - A week?
- It just happened then. - They came to Korea together...
- to have the wedding here. - Yes. It was for the wedding.
Did they have the wedding at the venue you checked out?
- They did. - They had it at that venue?
(The venue was selected carefully...)
(after his thorough inspection.)
Yes. You were half crazy that day.
- The ruler maniac. - You measured everything.
(They match.)
(I approve of this venue.)
(At the venue he approved of...)
The venue looks great.
- It's the perfect height. - Nice. You chose a great venue.
My sister-in-law was so happy with the venue. I felt so proud.
Sung Hwan was the MC.
- You were the MC? - I was.
He's in limelight with everything he does lately.
That'd be me. Nice to meet you. I'm Actor Ku Sung Hwan.
- Gosh. - He said that to introduce himself.
Other people are supposed to say that about him.
(Feeling shy)
- So... Yes. - I was the MC at the wedding.
"Groom Lee Ju Ang."
- "Bride..." - Nguyen.
I couldn't say her name.
- It was her full name. - I had to say her full name.
Nguyen is her family name. Minh Thu is her name.
Minh means smart and clever.
Thu means autumn.
- Smart autumn. - Minh Thu.
- Smart autumn. - Smart autumn.
- Ju Ang, do you want water? - Yes.
- Ju Seung, do you want water? - Thank you.
She's so cute.
I just washed my hands. Do you want some?
It's nice to see her...
in the video.
My gosh. His mother is smiling at her like a proud mom.
You know what?
- They seem happier together. - Yes.
- Right. - I can definitely see the change.
The atmosphere change after a wedding in the family.
You guys seem much happier.
Did you eat?
- A little bit earlier. - She's hungry.
He's still hungry.
I guess you like to eat in small bits,
- but multiple times. - Yes.
- In small bits? - She's from Vietnam.
She might not understand that.
Enjoy.
(She tears a small bit of the food and eats it.)
(They enjoy the bread together as a family.)
(Salivating)
Look at Coco.
Have you been well since the wedding?
We drove her parents to the airport today.
- I see. They left today. Right. - I see.
The wedding was quite hectic, wasn't it?
A bit. It was hectic.
My mother-in-law didn't speak Korean at all.
- Not even a word. - You took care of her.
It was her first time traveling abroad.
She had never been on a plane before our wedding.
- Gosh, she must've been so happy. - Really?
- Then she must've been happy. - This is big.
- She must've been. - Yes.
- She was happy. - She loved her trip.
She had Korean food for the first time too.
I see.
- So... - Where have you visited...
during your trip here? Have you been traveling a lot?
I've been to...
Jeju Island.
- Gosh. - Jeju Island.
- Suwon. - Suwon?
- Suwon. - Songdo, Incheon.
- How did she go there? - Songdo, Incheon.
Yes. I've been to Yangyang.
- Yangyang. - Yangyang.
I've been to the downtown area.
- The downtown area. - By that...
- Downtown? - Hongdae.
- Hongdae. Myeong-dong. - Myeong-dong.
- Sinchon. - Sinchon.
- She's been to many places. - Sinchon.
So she's been to popular places...
she saw on social media.
Of course, she must want to visit all these places.
Will you have dinner too?
- We should. - Okay.
- Have fun. - Okay.
Come home early.
I'll be home around 7pm.
- Come home early. - I'll be home around 7pm or 8pm.
Where's he going?
He said he had to wrap up some work stuff...
before heading back to Vietnam.
I decided to be her guide today.
- It's been a while. - Businessmen have a lot of work.
On a day like today,
your brother must've felt awful because...
- she would've been home alone. - Right.
But having Ju Seung as her guide would be lovely.
I hope Ju Seung did a good job as her guide.
(Worried)
That's the problem.
- Let's go. - Yes.
We have to get going right about now.
- Let's go. - Okay.
- Coco, I'll be back soon. - Okay.
I'm heading out first.
- Bye. - All right.
I'll be back, Coco.
- Are you ready? - Yes, I'm ready.
(Fixing her hair)
(They fix each other's clothes.)
- Gosh. - Oh, my.
- Their outfits look similar. - Right. You know what?
They seem to be getting along very well.
Does this not work with this outfit?
- Does it look weird? - So weird.
(Playful)
Whenever she comes to Korea,
she stays with my mom for over ten days.
So naturally, they've become quite close.
- That's nice. - It's wonderful.
His mother treats her like her own.
- I see. - Right.
So Thu feels comfortable around her.
But this one is loose on my head.
This is the perfect color, but it'd look weird when I put it on.
Is this better? Should I wear this?
I know that this color is a good match.
- Sure. - It suits the outfit the best.
- It suits the outfit the best? Yes. - Yes.
All right. Let's go. Bye, Coco.
Bye, Coco.
- Three. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
(Dashing away)
I'll be back, Coco.
You know what? Coco goes to her room...
when she knows we're leaving.
- She knows they're leaving. - Yes.
Actually, Coco might be happy that they're leaving.
(I have the house to myself.)
- She needs to regroup too. - Right.
She's been to so many places already.
- Where could you take her to? - Right.
I had a lot on my mind.
- Thu, your wedding in Vietnam... - Yes.
Was it last year or two years ago? I can't even remember.
Time flies by.
Has it been a year?
Which wedding did you like more? The one in Vietnam? Or in Korea?
- I liked the one in Korea. - What?
My makeup looked beautiful.
- My dress was beautiful. - Yes.
- So... Right. - It was all bling bling.
I researched everything for the wedding in great detail.
I even measured the height...
- of the platform. - Him and the platform height.
You liked it, right?
Thank you so much, Ju Seung.
I guess you asked her multiple times already.
- Right. - I asked her about three times.
That's a lot indeed.
Vietnamese has distinctive tones.
Right. She's speaking Korean like she's speaking Vietnamese.
Thank you so much, Ju Seung.
Did you study Korean for a year?
Five months.
- Five months? - Yes.
Then your Korean improved quite fast.
She spoke much better Korean compared to last year.
My Japanese isn't improving at all.
How can her Korean improve that fast?
- Kian84, what's monkey in Japanese? - Monkey.
"Saru."
That's all I know.
(I got my self-esteem back.)
How long have you been with my brother?
- Three years. - Three years?
Yes, three years.
Three years. So you dated for two years.
- Yes. - Then you got married in Vietnam...
- and in Korea after 1 year. - After 1 year... Yes.
Is my brother good to you?
He's so good to me.
What does he do for you?
Ju Ang is...
just nice to me.
He doesn't cheat on me. I hate that the most.
- That's the most important quality. - This is the most important.
He doesn't gamble.
- He doesn't gamble. - Right.
So it's because he doesn't do problematic things.
- You must be in love... - He just doesn't cause problems.
- to learn a language. - Right.
- Dating can help a lot. - That's true.
His shape is pretty.
- His shape is pretty. - His shape is pretty?
- Doesn't she mean he's handsome? - His shape is pretty.
- His shape... - You mean his face?
Yes. His face.
She's saying your brother is handsome.
- He's handsome. - His appearance.
(Hearing about his brother's secret for the first time)
Where are you going, by the way?
We'll be there in ten minutes.
(Korean Folk Village)
(Spotting it)
- Korean Folk Village? - I see.
Since she's in Korea,
she ought to visit the Korean Folk Village.
My sister-in-law hasn't been to the Korean Folk Village yet.
The first spot I took her to was the Korean Folk Village.
The name says it over there, Thu.
- Gyeonggi Province... Over there. - Where? I see.
"Korean Folk Village."
- It's 500m away. - Yes, Korean Folk Village.
- She can read everything. - You're good at reading too.
Could you read what's on the bottom too?
- Where? - The one on the bottom.
"Gyeonggi Arts Center."
Who's that? Someone is doing a concert here.
- Read the big letters. - Choi Baek Ho.
- What? - Choi Baek Ho.
(Choi Baek Ho)
She can read it.
- He's the symbol of romance. - Gosh, I'd love to go to that.
- He's amazing. - Right.
(With romance in the air...)
We've arrived.
(they arrive at the Korean Folk Village.)
(Opening the door)
Gosh, it's so sunny.
(Walking in the warm sunshine)
How are you feeling?
(Holding hands)
They seem so close.
They look like a mom and a daughter.
Right.
By the way, it looks like you two coordinated the outfits today.
No, we didn't.
Both of your outfits are in the color of autumn leaves.
This is the only outfit I have.
(Right?)
I want to wear an outfit in floral pink...
- Later... - or rose pink.
- Rose pink. - I want to wear pink outfits too.
But I don't have any.
- Come on. - "Buy me one."
She wants to go to a department store, Ju Seung.
Why are you pretending not to hear her?
I have a hard time picking up on that.
- Why is that? - That's hard for me.
I thought they were talking to each other.
Have you ever held hands when you were out with your mom?
- Have you held her hand? - Gosh, sons don't do that.
- Have you done that? - What do you think?
(Me?)
I guess we have to buy the tickets here.
- We have to buy a ticket? - Yes.
Will you buy it?
He'll take care of it.
- He will? - Don't worry about that.
We have to use the kiosk for the tickets.
This is the one. We must use the kiosk.
Stay there. It's hot here.
You're doing a proper job as their guide.
(Buying the tickets)
This tree looks beautiful.
Yes. That's a beautiful color. It's so green.
Isn't your bag heavy, Mother?
It's not heavy.
Is yours heavy? Should we use the parasol?
- The parasol? Let's use it later. - It's way too hot.
She's good to your mother too.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Three people. - Welcome.
- Hello. Thank you. - Thank you.
It's the Korean Folk Village.
(He prepared this itinerary for a unique experience.)
There were so many foreigners.
Especially after "KPop Demon Hunters" premiered.
(Packed with tourists from all over the world)
Even the zoomers go to the Korean Folk Village these days.
To feel closer to a country, one has to learn about its history.
That's the process of getting to know a country.
As her guide for the day,
I'll take her to traditional places,
- so we can make memories together. - That's nice.
- There are many performances too. - The village has a lot of programs.
We must go to the Fabric Dye Street. Let's go to Section 14.
- This should be our route. - Where is it?
That way, we won't have to go around twice.
Let's go straight.
(Guide Ju leads them while checking the map.)
Is it a slow day here because it's a weekday?
Mother, did people make kimchi with that?
- People still store it in there. - They do?
- I see. Jangdokdae. - I see.
(Intrigued)
I saw that in many dramas.
- It's a thatched roof house. - That?
A thatched roof house.
When I was young,
I had houses like this in my neighborhood.
- Did you live in a house like this? - My house...
No. I used to live in a big house.
Houses used to look like this back in the day.
That's how spoons used to look back then.
Spoons improved over the years.
Spoons.
This is fascinating for her.
(Checking)
(He leads them while diligently studying the map.)
(Following)
We've reached the administrative office now.
(Guide Ju enters the office well ahead of them.)
You should walk with them. Why...
He's their guide.
He must feel impatient. He's in a hurry.
- Right. He wants it to be perfect. - Yes.
(His passion as their guide makes him walk faster.)
- Have you seen this in a drama? - In a drama?
- And he sounds manly today too. - Yes.
When you commit a crime,
- they... - They twist your legs there.
- Twisting the legs? - This is what happens.
(Demonstrating how one's legs get twisted)
- Have you not seen this? - I have.
- I've watched it in a Korean drama. - Back then, there was no evidence.
They couldn't take pictures.
They made criminals confess by this punishment.
This is where the punishment took place.
And the district magistrate would be sitting over there.
You're trying your best.
I've watched this in dramas.
Shouldn't you take a picture in the magistrate chair?
Not anyone could sit there.
If we were in the Joseon Era, you would've been punished.
(She goes to the magistrate chair as instructed by the guide.)
Listen up.
One, two, three.
Come here.
Listen up.
One, two, three.
Say, "Listen up."
What should I do, Mother?
- They get along so well together. - Right.
(Taking pictures of them enjoying the magistrate chair)
- This is funny. - What?
This is funny.
(After they finish looking around the administrative office, )
(he checks the pamphlet again.)
We need to go this way to reach the photo spot.
If we go this way...
This is it.
Wanhyangroo.
Wanhyangroo?
I bet it will be cool in here.
There's a lake here too.
(Wanhyangroo)
You know, aristocrats used to sing for entertainment.
This was the place of their entertainment.
(A nugak that offers a glimpse into the ancestors' taste for arts)
You explained it in easy terms.
She didn't know the details.
So I only explained simple things while we were there.
- I see. - I see. Okay.
(They get closer to the nugak, following the tune.)
There are so many foreigners.
(There are so many foreigners.)
(Wanhyangroo is filled with visitors.)
- Is there a performance? - Luckily, we went in...
when they were performing.
Great. This is excellent.
(Taking pictures)
(Guide Ju takes pictures of them during the performance.)
You're taking pictures of them in the back.
(A picture of them enjoying the performance)
(Engrossed in the performance, clueless of what he's doing)
That's cool.
That's a carp.
A fish?
That's a carp. It's a fish.
- There's a big one too. - A big one?
- This is the photo spot. - What?
- Let's take pictures here. - Here?
In the end, pictures are what last.
- Why don't you take one together? - Let's take one together.
Together.
- Make a heart. - I'll take it.
- One, two, three. - How?
- Oh, how lovely this is. - Yes, what a lovely sight.
Stand there, and I'll take a picture of you.
- I see. - By herself?
I don't know how to pose for it.
(An awkward pose)
Come this way.
(He tells her where to stand as she feels shy.)
One.
(An impressive change in her facial expression)
- Hold on. - At last.
- Hold on. Is she an influencer? - At last.
She's not an influencer?
There's finally someone who can understand me.
One.
Did you see her breathing technique?
- She held her breath. - Yes.
(KEY became someone else in front of a camera.)
Why...
That way, you'll look natural...
- in the photos. - Check out her gaze and shoulders.
(She's as classy as an idol star.)
- She looks captivating. - Yes.
One more time. Pull out your hand.
She's really not an influencer?
- No. - I see.
She just loves having her pictures taken.
(Busy)
- Right here. - Here?
- Does it look pretty? - One, two, three.
(She doesn't leave her hands alone for a moment.)
I could tell that she had experience posing in front of cameras.
There's a video that went viral.
She turned her fingers while posing for cameras.
This?
- Yes, I know. - Yes.
It's like she's a Living National Treasure...
when it comes to posing for cameras.
My brother told me that...
on a daily basis, she usually takes...
about 500 to 1,000 pictures.
(She's serious about taking pictures.)
- She looks beautiful. Oh, my. - My gosh.
Having her pictures taken is her only hobby.
When they got married in Vietnam,
my brother's eyes were almost out of focus...
because they took so many pictures.
This is why!
Look at the picture. He was holding his phone that day.
- Look. - My gosh!
(A tight grip)
- Grooms don't usually carry phones. - He was holding his phone.
- You're so sharp! - Yes.
Seriously. He's so sharp.
(Exactly, my point.)
I've never seen a groom holding a phone at his own wedding.
I found out that she really loved being photographed.
I thought that we should do something she'd enjoy the most.
That's why I took them to a place...
- with a lot of photo spots. - That's great.
Our show has Mootographer.
But just for today, I'm Jutographer.
He's stealing Hyun Moo's thing.
- Gosh, he can't steal that from me. - What?
It's about time I took it from him.
I don't consider phone cameras as real cameras.
(Clicking)
I'm Jutographer.
(I'm Jutographer.)
- Click. - That's a different pose.
My gosh.
(Jutographer is at work.)
(She showcases a variety of poses like the Living National Treasure.)
- Gosh, Minh Thu is so cool. - Oh, my.
(I'm determined to take great pictures.)
That's giving me the creeps.
One, two, three.
(He spreads out his legs to take her pictures.)
You look like a pro.
(Jutographer doesn't stop taking pictures.)
How do they look?
- She's checking them right away. - She's checking them right away.
(What do you think?)
Gosh, you're good.
- Did they come out well? - They look great.
(His sister-in-law loves the pictures.)
It looks a bit blurry.
- You should've wiped the lens. - Right. You should have.
No, this degree of blurriness is fine.
Aligning the water at her waist level...
makes her legs look longer.
- That's good. It's a nice photo. - I can't align it at her neck.
- Okay. - You've got some skills.
They look great.
- You're good. - Yes.
Okay.
(I'm proud of you, Jutographer.)
Next...
(Looking around to find the next spot)
This place is beautiful too.
What's that? Is it a tombstone?
Let's take one here.
Yes. This tree is beautiful.
Could you stand over there? Let me take pictures of you.
When I spotted good lighting for pictures,
- I took pictures of her right away. - Gosh.
Here? How?
(Feeling shy again)
I'll let the light flow in.
One, two, three.
(Her gaze changing)
(Feeling proud)
I can't align that at your neck. Hold on. From here...
One, two, three.
- Gosh. She's a natural. - One, two, three.
Okay.
- It will adjust the lighting soon. - But...
See? It's adjusting the lighting.
I love that kind of lighting in my photos.
You can see it partially.
Doesn't it look great?
It looks awful.
I'm glad if you don't like it.
- I like it. - You take good pictures.
Why are your pictures all tilted?
- AI can fix the alignment. - AI can do it.
I used the pro mode.
Doesn't it look good?
You're a good photographer.
- Even she's taking pictures. - She's walking too.
(The photo shoot with professionals continue.)
- Should we sit down for a bit? - Let's take a break.
(They take a short break after taking tons of pictures.)
Mother, do you want to go to the restroom?
- Do you want to go? - Sure. I should use it too.
- The restroom? - Yes.
It's fun to go to the restroom together.
(Jutographer is left all alone.)
Oh, my legs.
(Sprawled out)
- Gosh, he must be tired. - Yes.
(Let me take a short break.)
(Closing his eyes)
- Did you really doze off? - Yes, because it was breezy there.
If you dozed off,
- they were gone for a while then. - Yes.
What's taking them so long?
I guess they abandoned you and left without you.
I almost fell asleep.
There they are.
They're coming back.
- What? - What?
What?
- Did she change her outfit? - She changed her outfit.
Did you change your outfit?
Yes, because we're taking pictures.
- For pictures? - For pictures.
She always carries several outfits...
- in the trunk of her car. - Really?
She's always ready to change her outfit.
For Minh Thu, this is an international trip.
- Right, it is. - Yes, it is.
- She's never been here before. - Right.
- Of course. - She must want to dress up for it.
I can totally understand. She belongs to my club.
It's like her photo shoot as the broom-to-be.
Right, the dress.
(A heavy suitcase is inevitable for photo maniacs.)
You look beautiful.
Is it heavy?
(She walks out confidently to score the best pictures.)
- She's serious about pictures. - Thank you.
For real.
(From the matching beige outfit with her mother-in-law...)
(to a bright pink outfit)
- She brought another pair of shoes? - Of course.
(She changes her style from head to toe.)
(Amazed)
You seem sick of it.
- That's why you took so long. - Where should we take pictures?
- I'll take one for you. - With Mother?
- You go ahead. Do it without me. - Let's take one by yourself.
- My mother... - Yes.
Hates taking pictures.
(He starts taking pictures with two phones.)
You're taking pictures with two different phones?
Two, three.
(Jutographer records memories of his new family member.)
Over there. Yes.
These pictures look great.
I think they came out well.
Gosh, you're good.
- Do you like them? - "You're good."
- Pictures here look great. - Yes.
Yes. The colors really pop. How beautiful.
If you don't like them, I can take them again.
- I like them. Yes. - You do?
(Showing off the pictures to her mother-in-law)
The pink outfit looks better in pictures.
Let me take a picture of you.
- Her too? - My gosh.
(Striking up a pretty pose in front of her mother-in-law)
- You're helping her make memories. - Yes.
Your mother likes taking pictures of her too.
She never had a daughter.
- You're always smiling. - This spot looks great.
(He keeps snapping photos wherever they go.)
It looks like your brother fabricated a fake meeting.
(Stuttering)
(Ju Ang didn't sound sure of himself.)
I think he left on purpose.
He wanted a break?
Did he go to the hospital to get his thumb checked out?
Maybe, his thumbprint faded away.
I bet his phone is always heated.
Did you take a lot of pictures?
I snapped about 40 pictures.
Then there's at least one good picture.
- Thank you. - Check them, please.
You're trying your best.
Good job.
You really took a lot of pictures.
(A whole heap of memories from today's trip)
- Let's take a selfie here. - Here.
- You've taken enough pictures now. - One, two, three.
(This is the final picture for the day.)
This place is peaceful, by the way.
It's quiet and peaceful.
We're here, so let's check out the gift shop.
(She goes inside while holding her mother-in-law's hand.)
(Traditional souvenirs)
Traditional Korean products are so popular these days.
They don't look tacky.
- They look gorgeous. - They're high-quality.
- Earrings? - Are they earrings?
Yes. Earrings are great.
Should I buy a pair?
That color looks the best on you.
Check them for me then.
(Guide Ju carries their bags while they shop.)
- Blue? Get them if you like them. - This one.
(She loves the earrings.)
Do you need anything?
This is cute. A hairband.
It seemed she felt bad,
- so I asked her more proactively. - That's good.
- You need to do that. - Yes.
- That's a cute apron. - Which one do you like?
You look beautiful. It's like you're wearing hanbok.
- That's nice. - It looks beautiful on you.
- It brightens her face. - I want that.
(Scowling at him)
Yes. Something like that. Get one.
This is good.
- Yes. Those pouches are cute. - How beautiful.
This is cute.
It's a brooch.
This is a beautiful color.
Get two.
- You lose them often. - Let's just buy one.
- Are you sure? - You can get two.
- I'm serious. - I'll just get one.
She must get them while they're there.
- Just 1. - No, get 1 more.
- Get more. - Get one more.
- We don't know when we'll be back. - Let's just buy one.
- How about this? - Let's just get one more.
- This one. - She can't visit Korea often.
- Okay? - So I want to spoil her when I can.
That's good.
- That's 79 dollars. - Okay.
That was good of you. You ought to buy them...
- while you're there. - Thank you.
- She can't find them in Vietnam. - Let's go.
- Let's get going now. - Okay.
Go and have a delicious meal now.
(The sky turns dark in no time.)
You didn't turn off the AC, right?
- Mother, are you hot? - Yes.
- Ju Seung. - It's hot in the back.
(Blast the AC, please.)
What kind of food have you had in Korea so far?
Pork backbone stew.
- Pork backbone stew. - Yes.
Bulgogi.
- She always gets certain dishes. - Ginseng chicken soup.
Ginseng chicken soup.
Yes. And I like pork belly.
Pork belly.
I like only meat.
You like only meat?
(She loves meat only.)
She's a meat lover.
- Yes. - Right.
- She's a total meat lover. - She's a meat lover.
She loves meat.
There was a Vietnamese song...
that went viral online.
Someone posted that on social media.
(Playing the song)
It's the song with this dance.
Yes, the one with the dance.
Yes, this is the song.
(I know this song. It's "See Tinh.")
- It goes like "Tinh tinh dan dan." - Yes, that's the one.
What? Tinh tinh dan dan?
This is a great song.
Okay, we're here.
(Where have they arrived, all excited?)
Okay. Let's go inside.
- What is this place? - Let's go inside.
Where did they go?
Gosh, this place is huge.
(This place is huge. I love it here.)
I love it here.
It's more beautiful at night.
(Past the door lies a camping area with a cool, hip vibe.)
- How beautiful. - This place looks nice.
Since it was a special day,
we didn't go to a regular barbecue place.
I chose a barbecue place that had the vibes of a campground.
(Guide Ju's pick)
(A barbecue at the campground)
There are barbecue places like that these days.
- That's right. - There's one in my neighborhood.
It isn't easy to go on a camping trip.
- That's right. - So, people just enjoy the vibes.
My mom has weak teeth,
so she can't eat pork belly.
She likes eels and such.
- Do they sell eels? - Eels are tender.
Thus, I picked a place with eels for my mom.
As for my sister-in-law,
she likes meat such as pork belly.
That was why I picked a barbecue place with both items.
If you stay here,
I'll go and buy meat.
Please take a seat. I'll be back.
Mom, what do you want to drink?
She only drinks water.
- Do you want tea? - Water.
Water, please.
- Water? - Yes.
- Water? - Water, please.
How about you?
- How about one beer? - Of course.
- Canned beer? - How about 1 beer and 1 soju?
What? Hold on.
- Will she drink somaek? - Will she drink somaek?
Okay.
Get what you want.
Your mom knows what she wants.
She's so much fun.
She's like a friend.
(This place is nice.)
This place is nice.
- Pork belly. - The mart looks nice.
There's even a handcart.
I didn't know about such places. It's fascinating.
Those places are trendy.
It'll feel like you're camping.
The weather is improving too.
Does Mom really want to drink somaek?
Where are the eels?
We par-grill them.
- That's nice. - Do you par-grill them?
Then I'd like to order one.
What?
(They go over the photos from the Korean Folk Village.)
(Let me see them.)
My daughter-in-law.
- They get along nicely. - Yes, they're sitting like...
- the mom and the daughter. - This one.
- It's so nice. - She's like an older sister.
It's better.
Let's keep taking such photos.
(Coughing)
The weather gets cold in no time. You should zip it up.
The weather gets cold in no time.
Here.
Ju Seung's mom must find her cute.
Thu is very good to her mother-in-law.
- Mother. - Answer the phone.
Hello.
Thu, have you eaten?
- We arrived at the restaurant. - Right now...
- We arrived at the restaurant. - Really?
Yes.
- Did you have fun? - I had fun.
I had so much fun.
Ju Seung's brother is very sweet.
I know. He's very good to his wife.
- All right. - Okay.
I see that he's well-rested.
(Did he sleep soundly?)
His skin is milky white.
I think he woke up from a nap.
- Seriously. - I think he went to the sauna.
I think he went to the sauna. His complexion looks healthy.
- He went to the sauna. - He went to the sauna.
(Ju Seung comes back with food.)
I'll go and help Ju Seung.
- What? - I'll go and help Ju Seung.
All right.
(They lift the handcart together.)
She works fast.
(She sets up the table.)
It looks delicious.
(He trusts his sister-in-law to set up the table.)
(Pork belly goes over the grill.)
Ju Seung, watch your hands.
His hands are precious since he needs to take photos.
"Your hands are precious."
"Take 500 photos later."
(Your hands are precious. Take 500 photos later.)
- Shall we do it together? - No, I'll do it.
Since the heat is too strong, I should be careful.
That's right.
- He's a dependable brother-in-law. - Ju Seung is good at such things.
(Sizzling)
It smells so good.
(Excited)
We're hungry.
I'm nearly done. Please wait a bit longer.
- It looks tasty. - How nice.
- It looks good. - Go ahead and eat.
Thank you.
(He grills the next item.)
- Eels. - They look tasty.
(Eels for Mom)
- Is this small enough? - He cuts them well.
- That's good. - He did a good job.
- Ju Seung is good at cooking. - It looks tasty.
- Ju Seung is good at cooking. - Yes.
- Enjoy the food. - The green onion kimchi is insane.
(He tries the pork belly with green onion kimchi.)
The green onion kimchi was so tasty.
It looks tasty.
(Impressed)
I love pork belly.
- Pork belly? - Yes.
(Getting up)
Ju Seung, you're good.
There you go.
- You're good. - You rarely stay seated.
Your butt must be light.
(Mom, I made it with the golden ratio.)
- Mom, don't drink too much. - Okay.
Will only your mother drink?
My sister-in-law can't drink at all.
She can't drink.
Let's clink our glasses.
Please love each other forever and ever.
Cheers.
(They enjoy the drink.)
This is how you eat it.
Seasoned green onion and green onion kimchi.
Pork belly is just an addition.
(He makes a pork belly wrap with great care.)
- Will you make her a wrap? - Onion too.
Judging by the size, it's for him.
- No, it looks like... - No, it's for him.
It's too big.
(The wrap is too big.)
(The gigantic wrap goes into Ju Seung's mouth.)
You knew exactly who it was for.
I know him well.
I don't make wraps for other people.
(Impressed)
This one is tasty too.
She eats with gusto.
- Gosh, it's a king-sized wrap. - She's eating it like a burger.
- What? - My goodness.
(She copied her brother-in-law's wrap.)
She didn't eat vegetables at all last time.
She is eating it today thanks to you.
(Proud)
(Thanks to the considerate choice in the menu, )
(Ju Seung's mom enjoys the tender eels.)
I can tell that she likes them.
Next month, the two of us will go and eat them.
- Eat what? Eels? - We'll go and eat eels.
- You and Ju Seung's mom? - Ju Seung's mom.
- Without Ju Seung? - Ju Seung won't go.
(Ju Seung won't go.)
- Really? - Will she go and eat eels...
with you, not Ju Seung?
They've talked about eating eels...
- for months. - It has been months.
But Sung Hwan postponed it.
Ju Seung's mom and I drink often.
We drink at Ju Seung's place when he's not around.
- Then I go, "I'll get going now." - Oh, my.
We do that.
- That's so nice. - We eat together often too.
- It's so fascinating. - I bet they get along well.
That's the best.
(She enjoys eels with her family...)
(before the meeting with her friend.)
(Glancing over)
(She eats a piece of eel just like her mother-in-law.)
The eels are tasty.
- Hundred points? - Hundred points.
How was the Korean Folk Village?
It was so much fun.
How were the photos?
You took incredibly pretty photos.
Do the photos look okay?
Ju Seung takes nice photos.
- What's this? - Did I take them well?
(Getting up)
That's a nice photo.
You look so pretty.
That's an amazing photo.
(She stares at the photo because she likes it.)
- It's a pretty photo. - It's a nice shot.
- You can... - It's the best.
You can edit it later.
Is she editing it already?
She's editing it to make it the best photo.
Apparently, it takes one minute to edit a single photo.
- It takes no time. - If she waits, she'll forget.
That's right.
Why did you stretch the legs so much and make yourself 180cm tall?
- Okay. - It looks good.
It's a nice photo.
- It's a nice photo. - It really is.
I captured...
the sky and trees perfectly.
It's the best photo.
- If you were going to edit it, - Send it to me.
One photo would've been enough.
(Smiling)
You take 1,000 photos and get 1 good one.
Send me the photos.
- I sent them to you. - Okay.
Now that my sister-in-law joined the family,
we gained a family member.
I feel like...
- the family became more amicable. - That's right.
My mom and I...
don't go out by ourselves often.
Thanks to this excuse, I got to travel with my mom.
My sister-in-law and I spent time together...
and got closer.
It was rewarding.
- Ramyeon is a must when you camp. - You have to eat ramyeon.
It looks so tasty.
It's the tastiest.
My goodness.
At a place like that, you can eat ramyeon even when you're full.
- Yes, you can. - Of course.
(Ju Seung's sister-in-law slurps the noodles as well.)
It's tasty.
Is it tasty?
When you visit in winter, let's go skiing together...
if you have time.
- That sounds good. - Yes.
My brother should come as well.
(I Live Alone)
(Late Summer Greetings)
Autumn is coming at last.
(KEY is going somewhere in a car.)
(Is he headed to his parents' place?)
- Did you drive to Daegu? - Yes, I drove there.
- It has been a while, right? - Yes.
(He drives past the farming area under the cloudy sky.)
I drove past Daegu and went to Yeongcheon.
(He drives past Daegu and goes to Yeongcheon.)
It's rare for you not to listen to music...
- during the drive. - You're right.
Where is he going?
I'm here.
(Is it raining?)
It isn't raining.
(He carries something with both hands.)
What?
(He walks over to someplace.)
(A resting place for the patriots)
It's a national cemetery in Yeongcheon.
This place is where the war veterans,
soldiers,
and people of national merit rest.
My grandparents are buried here.
My paternal grandparents.
My grandpa fought in the Korean War.
- That's impressive. - He was discharged...
due to an injury.
He took a bullet in his ankle.
For his nation, he fought with all his might.
I realized much later...
that only a select few received...
recognition from the nation.
September is a meaningful month for me,
so I visited them to say hello...
for the first time in a long while.
My father is also a man of merit. He fought in the Vietnam War.
- Did he fight in the Vietnam War? - Yes.
My hometown is the Sipjaseong Town.
Sipjaseong Town.
(The place where he met his neighbor who is a war veteran, Mr. Ddol)
(Sipjaseong Town is a town for the people of national merit.)
(Many neighbors live with injuries from the war.)
My paternal grandpa fought in the Korean War.
His younger brother was an officer during the Korean War,
so he's buried in a different national cemetery.
My maternal grandpa fought in the Vietnam War.
He's buried in a different cemetery in Daejeon.
You come from a family of patriots.
- That's right. You must have pride. - I have pride.
I did my military service at the Seoul National Cemetery.
That's right.
- You're a patriotic idol. - Yes.
- "A patriotic idol." - "A patriotic idol."
You should perform at national events.
- "A patriotic idol." - Hey, we'll give you a gold badge.
Give me a patriot's badge.
- Seriously. Thank you, KEY. - Thank you.
(Kian84 means his words.)
(He drops by at a place before visiting his grandparents.)
Hello.
(They sell silk flowers for the graves.)
(Staring)
- Are those real flowers? - Yes.
People use silk flowers for the graves in the mountain...
and use real flowers for the columbarium.
- It must be because of the weather. - Yes.
- It rains outside. - That's right.
- Silk flowers look good for years. - That's right.
(Since these flowers are for his grandparents)
- So... - That's right. Make a big bouquet.
(He combines the colors carefully.)
Hold on.
- They're pretty. - Will this be okay?
Yes. That looks good.
(He holds the flowers that will never wither.)
"The flowers that will never wither."
- Bye. - Take care.
(He goes to see his grandparents now.)
(He holds the flowers in his arms.)
Their graves were pretty far up.
(He goes through the past memories of visiting them...)
(and walks over to them.)
You did a good thing.
It has been a while.
It's huge.
- The place makes you reverent. - That's right.
We often forget...
- that we owe our lives to them. - That's right.
I have so much gratitude and respect for them.
(He's nearly at his grandparents' graves.)
There they are.
Have you been well?
My goodness.
(Kim Jae Kwan, Sergeant First Class of the Army)
Are your grandparents buried at the same place?
My grandpa's grave was there first. When my grandma passed away,
- they could be put side by side. - They could do that for them.
The period my grandpa fought in the war...
It's written on the tombstone.
- All the information is there. - Yes.
He went through a lot.
Fighting in a war for over a year...
(My goodness)
Training for 5 day and 4 nights makes me feel like I'm dying.
I know.
You know, there's something I still remember.
When "Taegukgi: Brotherhood of War" came out,
my family went to the theater together.
Grandparents cry while watching that movie.
My grandpa cried so much that he couldn't watch the movie.
- Really? - Yes.
He said the movie didn't capture 1-10th of the brutality...
- he had experienced. - Of course not.
You can't show that properly in a movie.
I was in elementary school then, but the memory is still fresh.
"That's my younger brother."
That was sudden.
- It's a line from the movie. - Go and take a nap.
No, it's a line from "Taegukgi: Brotherhood of War."
"That's my younger brother." Then he cries.
It's a scene from the intro of "Taegukgi: Brotherhood of War."
(The grandparents and their grandson meet for the first time in a while.)
The rain stopped so that I could say hello.
- He's using a dialect naturally. - Yes.
(He gives them the pretty flowers he has prepared.)
(He hurriedly spreads out a mat on the ground.)
Have you been well?
Your grandparents must've been happy.
Yes, they must've been happy.
(Next to his grandparents are the grave of a Vietnam War veteran.)
- We wouldn't be here without them. - That's right.
(He wipes off the rainwater.)
It rained every day back then.
- It stopped at the right moment. - Yes.
Your grandparents must've helped...
for your comfort.
(Their grandson prepared food to show his love.)
- Dried pollack. - Yes.
Although it's a simplified version, you have the necessary items.
(He pours them alcohol for the first time in a while.)
You guys can't drink much.
You should share it.
Are those rings for them?
(Joking)
- Hold on. It's my first time... - Will they like the rings?
Seeing someone put rings on the table for the dead.
- Are they for your grandparents? - No.
You put them on the table.
- They did like jewelry. - If they liked it...
- Some people might misunderstand. - Right.
- I took them off to say hello. - I see.
(He shows his manners in front of his grandparents.)
My goodness.
(He bows to them for the first time in a while.)
I bet they cherished him a lot.
(The grandson they cherished, KEY is here.)
My goodness.
(KEY sits comfortably next to his grandparents.)
There weren't a lot of people since it was too early.
When you go there,
your heart aches. You feel sad.
They loved me so much.
In my family,
both my mom and dad worked.
So, my grandparents took care of sending me off to school,
picking me up from school,
and making my meals.
Thus, I actually spent more time with my grandparents...
than my parents in elementary school.
I loved my grandma's food a lot.
Even after I grew up,
I always hung out with my grandma...
in both Daegu and Seoul.
I have many memories of such dates.
(His grandma even watched his debut performance.)
- How nice. - It was the day I debuted.
(KEY still remembers...)
(his Grandma's braised crab in soy sauce.)
- That's right. You made it. - You told us about it.
(Now, KEY is big enough to cook it for his parents.)
(Even when he traveled alone)
(On Buddha's Birthday?)
(The word he hasn't heard in a while...)
(made him immediately think of his grandma.)
My birthday is in September.
But my grandma's death anniversary is...
the same as my birthday.
She passed away after I reached adulthood.
For 2 to 3 years after her death,
I didn't even want to see a cake.
It was a hectic situation.
She wasn't sick at all.
She passed away suddenly in her sleep.
(His grandma passed away suddenly.)
For 2 to 3 years, I was so depressed.
But then I thought,
"Would she want me to be like this?"
- Right. - I had that thought.
Since then, I just go through the past memories...
- or the happy moments. - That's right.
Her death anniversary coincided...
- so that you'd think about her. - That's right.
The meaning has changed.
You're such a good grandson.
In any case, it's still a strange day for me.
You're right.
Gosh, it's raining right after greeting them.
- Is it raining now? - It started to rain.
(The rain falls as it was waiting right after he greets them.)
(He sits with them with the umbrella he brought.)
You look like a kid sitting there like that.
Well,
I'm sure it was a massive coincidence,
but my grandmother hated me being under the rain.
So whenever it rained,
she waited for me at school before school ended.
Every single time.
- She must've adored you so much. - Right.
It rained like crazy starting from Seoul.
It rained endlessly.
"I won't be able to make deep bows to them with the mat."
I kept thinking this as I drove, but as I arrived...
You can't hold onto the umbrella when you make deep bows.
Right.
She didn't want her grandson to get wet from the rain.
- That's fascinating. - Right.
After seeing it rain again,
I thought, "You want me to leave now?"
She wanted you to leave without staying too long.
She got a good look of you.
"You want me to come again? Okay."
Why is it raining so much again all of a sudden?
Grandmothers always hurry you out.
- Right. - "Hurry up and go."
They love it when you stay the night,
- but they always tell you to go. - Right.
- They send you away. - Right.
(He cleans up as his grandmother tells him to.)
You're not allowed to leave a small amount of food, right?
You're not allowed to do that.
Alcoholic drinks can't be thrown out as well.
You have to take them with you.
It was called the gosure back then to make small food offerings...
and food was left for animals to eat.
The gosure isn't done any more?
Anything that harms the grave can't be done.
(The place he stayed for a while gets cleaned up neatly.)
I'll get going.
I know how it feels when you say, "I'll get going."
It breaks your heart.
(He heads back even though he wants to stay longer.)
But just paying them a visit...
would've felt...
- really refreshing. - Right.
(Your grandson, Ki Bum, will be back again.)
(He leaves the national cemetery with his things.)
- Gosh. - My heart still feels full...
because I paid a visit to them.
That must be great.
You must feel relieved.
(A short but meaningful meeting with his grandfather and grandmother)
(Let's see.)
(He goes past the tollgate of North Yeongcheon.)
(He drives toward Daegu?)
You're not heading back to Seoul.
Right.
(He gets closer to the center of the city.)
(It's raining a lot.)
- It rained a lot. - Right.
It's raining after Dae Ho washed his car.
You're right.
(The rain gets stronger as he arrives.)
It's raining a lot.
(Looking around)
(KEY makes a call to someone while looking around.)
Mom!
Welcome.
Gosh, Mom.
Gosh, it's been a while since I saw her.
- Right. - It's been a while.
- My goodness. - I have to wait so long...
to see my son.
(This January, KEY's mother retired...)
(after working in a hospital for 36 years.)
(KEY was with her on her last day at work.)
She went through so much to work for 36 years.
Definitely. That was amazing of her.
(He helped his mother clear up her desk.)
(He stayed with her during her last moment at work.)
She looked so nice.
In September, there's my birthday,
my grandmother's death anniversary,
and Chuseok happens around that time as well.
I wanted to take care of all of those dates,
but we were always busy during Chuseok.
I haven't been able to spend time for my birthday for a while.
While I was there, I wanted to spend time for my birthday...
and visit my grandmother...
and grandfather.
- That's great. - That's great...
to spend time on your birthday with your mother.
The one who should be congratulated during that person's birthday...
is that person's mother.
Right.
- Should we use one umbrella? - We could use mine.
- Do you want to put that away? - Okay.
Put in here.
Give me just a moment.
- Their shirts match! - Right.
Gosh, did you two wear matching shirts on purpose?
No. It was a coincidence.
- Really? - No way!
- It was really a coincidence. - That's fascinating.
That happens all the time.
There are times when our outfits feel similar.
Do you share the same clothes with your mother?
No. That doesn't happen.
When my mom is wearing jeans,
I'm wearing jeans too.
That's great to see.
- Even the pants are the same. - Right.
- The outfits look really similar. - We really didn't plan for that.
Wearing matching shirts with your mother gives me goosebumps.
You should do that with your mother too.
- Wearing matching clothes with her. - We have different fashion tastes.
- What does she like? - Different fashion tastes?
What does she like?
Clothes for mothers.
- They'll look good on you too. - They'll look good on me?
- I should find something then. - You should.
All right.
- Should I put it in your bag? - Sure.
Open it up first.
- Okay. - There we go.
Hold on.
- Let's go. - Gosh.
They're arms are linked too.
You should do those things for your project of being a good son.
- Linking arms? My gosh. - Right.
That's really nice to see.
So the arms weren't linked to avoid the rain, right?
- What? - Gosh.
Don't pretend you understand him, Kian84.
Can you link arms with your mother?
It happens from time to time.
- Does your mom hold your arm? - She holds my arm.
- I pretend not to know about it. - But...
- You pretend not to know about it? - I just ignore it.
- Because it's awkward. - What is that?
Your body would stiffen.
When I met Grandma,
- it didn't rain at all. - Really?
I was worried about you being under the rain...
- while visiting the cemetery. - No.
- It stopped right when I visited. - Right.
It rained a little when I left.
- Really? That's a relief. - Right.
Not a single person was there.
Right.
As Chuseok is approaching,
- there will be a lot of visitors. - More visitors will come soon.
Right. It would be quiet on a day like today...
- without many visitors. - Gosh.
Have I grown, or has this place shrunk?
So this is how it's like?
This is downtown Daegu.
- Dongsung-ro? - Right.
Has it been around 15 years since I have come?
(Daegu's biggest main street and landmark in the 1990s)
Hotels, restaurants,
cultural activities, arcades, shopping, and department stores.
All of those things were enjoyed there.
When you live in the provinces,
there's just one place to go to...
- when you want to hang out. - Right.
- Downtown. - Right.
Everyone meets people downtown.
- There's nowhere else to go. - Right.
As of right now,
I heard that there were many other places to visit.
But it was only Dongsung-ro for me back then.
It's the place for the young generation.
I've heard about it so many times.
There's even a song that is called "Dongsung-ro."
During our times,
there was a group called the Dongsung-ro Sisters.
They became popular for singing on that street...
and that area became popular as well thanks to them.
Daegu has a lot of great food too.
- Of course. - Right.
(There are still many customers...)
(who look for the representative dishes of Dongsung-ro.)
There's the tteokbokki. Pepper tteokbokki.
Gosh, that looks good.
You know that many franchises started there, right?
- Mexicana and Hosigi. - Mexicana and Hosigi.
- Sinjeon Tteokbokki. - Sinjeon Tteokbokki.
- Seoga and Cook too. - Mexicana?
- Chicken franchises. - Tteokbokki as well.
- Right. - Really?
This place is the origin of Korea's fried chicken.
- Right. - Wasn't that Suwon?
- No. - Suwon is known for its galbi.
- No. - There's everything there.
- There are places to eat too. - Right.
Do you know your way around here?
- You don't remember this place? - I don't.
We met earlier at the square.
That was where Jungang Police Substation was.
- It must've been removed. - "Realize a just society."
- I see. - You couldn't tell at all, right?
- Things change whenever you visit. - Right.
- It's different all the time. - New places are built.
There's the sign for "Debec" over there.
You're right.
It's strange as it's closed now, right?
- Daegu's department store? - Debec.
(Daegu's department store is currently closed.)
(It was full of people in the past as Daegu's biggest shopping mall.)
- Gosh. - Look at all of those people.
It went wild for Christmas.
The atmosphere must've been great.
Another famous department store...
struggled because of this place.
- They all went there. - Right.
The people in Daegu only went there.
Strangely enough, the people in Daegu...
were really loyal to this place.
This place was a rendezvous.
It was a rendezvous...
and all luxury items were bought there.
Debec was in charge of many art competitions...
and dance competitions for the youth.
That building was huge back then.
- It was only that big. - Right.
That building looked small to me now.
Right.
It's KEY!
- It's KEY! - Hello.
- Hello. - Hello.
That's a great thing to see.
"KEY!"
His fashion looks extraordinary.
You're hungry, aren't you?
I am.
There's a famous gimbap place here. Do you want to go there?
- Really? Let's go. - It's right there.
- You've never been there. - I love places like that.
- It's her favorite place. - A restaurant loved by locals.
It has a clean taste.
It was a place I never went to before.
Hello.
Feel free to take a seat.
- Right. - Hello.
There's always a line here.
- Here? - Yes.
- Is that so? - Where should we sit?
Should we sit there?
Gosh, it looks good even by a glimpse of it.
Gosh, this place is good.
Do you know that place?
No. The rice looks good.
The rice looks good?
The burdock roots and the fishcakes.
We can tell right away by taking a look.
- What does that even mean? - What does that even mean?
- It doesn't make sense. - Well,
I just got too excited.
It was run for 47 years.
- Gosh. - The gimbap place?
- Gosh. - It was run for 47 years?
That's amazing.
We'll get a roll of gimbap and a bowl of udon.
A roll of gimbap and a bowl of udon?
- That's a great combination. - I've never heard about this place.
You wouldn't have heard about this place.
I came here often...
when I was working.
The food is great here.
It gets served right away.
The gimbaps were constantly rolled.
(Why has this place become her favorite place?)
It gets served right away.
The gimbaps were constantly rolled.
Gosh, that looks good. I liked old-style gimbaps.
- That must taste great. - That's perfect.
- That must be good. - Gosh.
That was amazing.
- I can imagine how the soup tastes. - Korean udon.
Korean-style udon.
(A tasty combination certified by his mother)
- Gosh, that looks good. - Thank you for the food.
Thank you for the food.
Give it a try.
I'll try the gimbap first.
It'll taste like the udon made in the past.
I'm not sure if you have tried this kind of udon.
(Satisfied)
Do you get what I'm saying?
- Well. - It's like the gimbap...
- for picnics. - Right.
- But it has a very clean taste. - Right.
Can't you feel the texture of the rice?
That must be so good!
- Right. - The rice is good.
That's the best gimbap.
It's strange how it's good without any meat.
(Enjoying a friendly conversation at his mom's favorite place)
It's not a shocking taste. There's no meat in it.
It just has fishcakes, burdock roots, and carrots.
- Gimbap for picnics? - Right.
- It's made in that style. - Each ingredient can be felt.
If my mom were to be a good cook in the 1970s,
it feels like the gimbap would've tasted like that.
You're so expressive. I can feel the taste right now.
Each grain of rice can be felt.
- Right. - Nothing tasted strong.
Right. Classic gimbap is great.
- Classic ones last forever. - Right.
(Tasting the gimbap of the past)
It must taste so good with the soup.
(He takes a sip of the udon soup.)
It's good.
- It's good, isn't it? - It tastes like old-style udon.
- Right? - Yes.
Should I get on the KTX or what?
(The taste that makes you want to head to Daegu impulsively)
It's good.
(It's good.)
Do you still have a lot of things to do after retirement?
- How has she been doing? - You seemed to be busy.
I'm busy.
- Really? - You're way too busy.
I kept being busy starting from last week.
Do you not feel bored?
I have to spend time with your dad...
two days a week.
(She's so romantic.)
They must get along really well.
I go to the cathedral to study as well.
I've been on trips almost every month.
- That must be great. - I'm loving it.
Don't I look much brighter?
- She looks relaxed. - I mentioned that.
Her complexion has gotten better.
It feels like her hair...
- has gotten more volume too. - Right.
I love that I feel so relaxed.
She must have had so many things she wanted to do.
Right.
It's great that you have come after a while.
I thought that it would be great for you to visit your grandparents.
Grandma and Grandpa would've loved to see you.
Right. I loved it too.
- Of course. - Right.
It had been years since I last visited.
- Are you done? - Shall we get going?
Let's go.
(Let's go outside and walk around.)
- I'll pay for it. - Okay.
- You two look like friends. - We're always like that.
- That's great to see. - Gosh.
My father...
wanted me to greet you instead.
(Feeling grateful)
- Since she's a regular. - Thank you.
- Goodbye. - I love those places.
Do you know the owner?
The owner here used to work in our hospital.
- Really? - Yes.
This much rain is okay.
- This will be a good memory. - Right.
President Jun, take a good look at those vibes.
The weather is terrible.
- No. - What are you saying?
- Matching outfits, - I see.
Linked arms, staying close to each other,
- and eating together. - It depends on the situation.
I'm sure Kian84 knows this as well.
Doing those things out of nowhere can have a negative effect.
Your mother might not like those things.
- Right. - We might get even more awkward.
It's better to look indifferent like Kian84 and I...
instead of forcing ourselves to do things.
- If we force ourselves... - But...
when I'm fine with my mom hold onto my arm.
- Are you drawing a line? - Are you drawing a line?
No.
We're just different.
- Right. You should draw a line. - What? We're similar.
I can't do things like carrying her on my back...
and saying things like, "I love you."
I can walk with my mom with our arms linked.
(Chuckling)
- Should we go this way? - Yes.
(Watching carefully)
What kind of place is this?
It's a place where you take pictures.
It's like the sticker photo booths in the past.
- Really? - Yes.
- The photobooth. - Do you want to give it a try?
Yes. Let's try taking photos too.
We can go in here.
Here?
(Full of excitement)
They have a lot of things here.
You're going to a photobooth with your mom?
- That's nice. - A photobooth with your mom?
I think it's great.
Oh, my gosh!
(Taking a look)
There are even combs prepared.
There are combs and hair irons.
- Really? - Yes.
- Have you been to these places? - I have.
- Really? - I've never done this before.
Take a look.
Let's take a look.
(Eyes shining)
Is there anything you want to put on?
Should I put on a hairband?
(He follows his mother.)
(I'll choose with you.)
It's a place she would never go to if it wasn't for her son.
- Right. - Right.
How is this one?
- Should we go with that one? - Yes.
- You should put this one on. - That's cute.
- Gosh. - Those ones are nice.
(Interested)
(What is it?)
(Grabbing)
- Should we put on the glasses too? - Yes.
We'll put the glasses on after the hairbands.
Right.
The children must lead them there.
Mothers would only go with their children.
(I can't watch this.)
There's a place for our belongings too.
- I'll put my purse down. - Right.
How is it done?
It's the same as just taking regular photos.
(Taking a look)
The bills have to be put in.
Credit cards can be used.
- Should we go with this one? - Sure.
(The son leads things smoothly.)
(She's just fascinated.)
- Where's the headband? - Here.
(Putting them on at the same time as if it was planned)
(He naturally makes a pose right next to his mom.)
(Smiling)
You have to look here.
Here!
You're really good at finding the camera lens.
(Embarrassed)
Try looking up here again.
There?
You're acting cute in front of your mom?
(His mother seems to look lost.)
- I keep looking at the screen. - Right.
Let's get a bit closer.
Here.
(Getting even closer)
(Reaching out her arm)
(She gently places her arm on her son's back.)
That's wonderful.
(Shy smiles of the mother and son who look just like each other)
- We have another one, right? - Yes. Take the hairband off.
Right.
- Right. One without anything. - Right.
(Holding each other a lot more affectionately)
- Their arms are over each other. - It feels so natural.
This is it!
Gosh.
- Why can't you do that? - Exactly.
- It's a fight against time. - Gosh, we're so busy.
Is it like this?
(Even though they feel busy with the counter, )
Done.
(they do their best to pose for each take.)
There's the heart.
My goodness.
- That's a tough one to do. - One more time?
Is it over?
Smile.
(She's really enjoying it even though it feels new to her.)
You should do that too.
Mothers love doing these things.
Gosh, these moments shouldn't be shown to the public.
- This one. - Two.
This one.
This is too much work for me.
This is nothing.
You can come and take pictures after having a meal.
Really?
It can be done after having a drink.
It felt awkward as I have never done this before.
I'll come again.
I should come with your dad.
- They must really get along. - That's great.
After doing it once with her like this,
she'll do it again with her friends.
- Right. - She has the experience now.
She's been through it once.
- Right. - She knows how it's done.
It's just that mothers have never tried these things.
(The result of her new experience is printed out.)
Two copies are printed like this?
You have your purse.
- Give it to me later. - Right.
(Her eyes are fixed on her first four-shot photo.)
This is fun.
- We should put these back. - Okay.
- Okay. - Let's go.
Right. They should be shown to these things.
My mom keeps all of those safe.
- Right. - Right.
(Feeling happy)
- They look great. - Right.
(An unforgettable memory saved)
It looks like they wore matching shirts just for this.
- Right. - Right.
That was just a coincidence.
These things are great.
Our parents enjoy doing the things we enjoy doing.
- Right. - Not the things they usually do.
There's no need to take them...
to a Korean table d'hote in Insa-dong.
- They could just be taken to... - Right.
A place like a pot rice place.
- Trendy places? - Right.
They enjoy going to those places even more.
I'm curious about this.
You all must have different methods...
of being a good son or daughter to your parents.
Giving them cash.
Well...
You went to the ATEEZ concert.
- Go with my mom? - She'll be happy to go with you.
Right.
As if she would feel excited about that!
- She'll be happy to go with you. - My mom?
You think she won't like it, right? She will be happy to go with you.
- My mom will like ATEEZ? - She will be happy about it.
- Right. - Right.
- I got my mom concert tickets... - She never had the chance to go.
And she went this week.
I give them tickets to all of my fellow hip-hop singers concert.
- Really? - And they like it...
because they're concerts...
- that they normally don't go to. - That's right.
They like the things that only we'd like to do.
I should send my mom to Stray Kids' concert.
- She'd love it. - That's right.
- Seriously, do it. - She'd sing "MANIAC."
- Maniac - Maniac
What's your way of showing filial love?
For me, it's dining out often.
- That's often. - You're a good son.
You wouldn't just eat. You'd talk with them too.
Seriously. I got a comment on it...
through Instagram.
"Ku Sung Hwan's family came to have a meal."
"They only ate the food and left."
Oh, without talking?
Like a gourmet club?
- You're like a foodie crew. - They really are.
(They came out to Dongsung-ro after making memories.)
There's the underground mall if you go down here.
- This is the bookstore, right? - Yes.
I remember this place.
Why did I come here so often?
Here? Didn't you come here to buy music albums?
I used to collect CD albums.
I bought all of them there.
(Young Ki Bum went there to buy CD albums.)
- Cassette tapes and CDs. - That's right.
- You came here to buy them. - You're right.
- You always came here for those. - How long has it been...
since you last went there?
Last time I went there was when I was 16.
- It's been really long. - There was no occasion to go there.
That's right.
I just went there to rest.
- To look around. - There are many things to do there.
Right. This is how it looked.
- You remember this? - Yes.
This is the underground mall.
- The mall is still here. - Of course.
It's just that there aren't many customers now.
Oh, thank you.
(Will it look the same?)
- This place is huge. - It is big. It's always been big.
(Packed with various stationery and items)
Time goes by really quickly...
- when you have some time to kill. - That's right.
My mom loves stationery.
- She keeps a journal too. - She keeps a journal.
(Parenting journal is a must.)
(KEY's mother still keeps a journal.)
She still writes a journal?
Why do you look so young there?
(Bitter)
- Kian84. - Kian84.
- My gosh. - I don't think...
you should do a marathon.
- It's the aftereffect, for sure. - You shouldn't run too much.
- You're right. - That wasn't so long ago.
- It isn't. - It's only three years ago.
You have a fair face and thick hair.
Does running make you age fast?
- I was surprised too. - Oh, my.
It's cute.
This is cute. Wallace and Gromit.
- This looks good. - People use keyrings a lot.
- Who cares? - This one's nice.
(Grabbing one as soon as she sees it)
You should get one too.
Yes, she'd pick one at ease at times like this.
I used to love stationery...
- when I was young. - I love it too.
- Really? - You can't help but take after her.
- Because she loves it... - A daughter-like son.
Oh, really?
- I still love it. - Me too.
I love things like this. Cards.
- You like maximal stuff. - Yes.
Your mother has the same taste as mine.
- She likes fully decorated ones. - This one's nice too.
- Get one each. - A girlish sentiment.
Gosh, it's a diary for ten years.
Do you want to get one?
Do you think...
- you can keep it for a year? - Of course.
- Your mom would. - You have to write it every day.
- I write it every day already. - She's already written it...
over ten years.
- Get one. - You should get one for her.
I'll get this.
It was not popular...
- that it was 70 percent off. - Of course.
People don't write a lot these days.
Most people don't dare buy it.
- A journal for ten years is... - But my mom...
My gosh. My mom loved it...
- as soon as she saw it. - People don't write these days.
- Right, let alone journals. - It suited my mom's taste the most.
There's no Hi-Tec-C pen. They were the best.
Oh, that pen brand?
- That's right. - I know.
It was a luxury.
If scary kids asked to let them borrow Hi-Tec-C pens,
I was really anxious...
- that they wouldn't return them. - That's because...
if you drop it,
the tip of the pen would go in, and you can no longer use it.
- That's right. - Right. You mean the tip.
- Gosh, seriously. - Those who were good...
at note-taking used that brand a lot.
The finer the tip, the more popular it was.
- Really? - Yes.
(Staring)
(They busily look around.)
She scans them while walking as well.
(She scans them while walking as well.)
- She keeps scanning. - Of course.
She loves them.
She scans them while walking to the counter.
Of course.
Oh, we pay here? It's a self-checkout?
(The son checks them out at the self-checkout.)
That's right.
- Use my card. - No, I'll pay.
- Really? Here. - Of course.
(She's proud of him.)
It's best to use the son's card.
I'm confident in writing a journal in it.
- I'm sure you can. - Yes.
It's really thick.
I should get some albums if they have them here.
(Looking around)
This must be it.
Is this it?
The section where they sell music albums...
- got a lot smaller. - People don't use them a lot now.
Gosh, the section for music albums...
- got a lot smaller. - It's a lot smaller, right?
This is my album too.
This one was released last time.
Where is the recent one?
They have the old ones.
- They must be sold out. - Yes.
Singers can check their own albums...
- if they go there. - That's right.
Do you have my album, "HUNTER?"
It's over there.
Oh, it's at the front?
Mom, it's at the front.
(Brightening up)
(Turns out KEY's album was displayed separately.)
You have a separate section.
My goodness!
- How nice for singers. - Look at this!
Mine was new, so they displayed it at the front.
You're totally in the center.
- Gosh, it's selling well. - I'm so proud of you.
I punched in the wrong address, so it went to your place.
She wrote down the wrong address.
I told her to get a new one while we were there.
- I see. - Get this.
It wouldn't feel so tense if there were too many displays.
- Right. It should be empty. - Yes, a little.
(Taking some away as though there are only a few left)
- That's right. - You should display them like that.
- As though it was selling well? - Of course.
Like they fell while people were grabbing them.
- Leave that. - Like this.
Does your mom buy your album with her money...
every time you release one?
She does.
- She buys ones for her friends too. - Really?
She gets some to keep for herself. One to open,
- and one to keep. - For collection.
- She buys them every time. - She could ask you.
I used to place the cartoons that I drew...
between books in the bookstore in my neighborhood.
I'd go and see if they were sold after school.
The thought itself is cute.
What price did you write on?
Similar to other items.
I set the price at 2.5 dollars.
I'd draw cartoons in my drawing book and place them.
You wanted to see if they'd be sold.
That'd be pricey now.
It'd be amazing...
- if you have the first edition. - If you have it...
That's a novel idea, though.
We have photo cards that we give out.
Photo cards?
You should get them.
- They didn't leave them out. - Thank you.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
Have a good day.
Let's go.
They made the most of their time.
You look like you lost more weight.
Your skin looks fairer.
- Come on in. - Home sweet home.
(Home sweet home)
- Son, it's been really long. - I'm home.
Last time you came was December last year.
- Mom, take this. - It's been more than six months.
It's really not easy to go to your parents' in another city.
I'll go get changed. You should get some rest too.
(Yawning)
You yawn automatically when you're at your parent's, right?
- You get sleepy. - Yes.
Goodness.
My gosh.
(Groaning)
(Grunting)
You drove there and walked around the whole day.
You must've been tired.
(He puts away the stuff he chose with his mom.)
(Flopping)
If you sleep now, your day could get messed up.
Your bed at your parents' makes you sleepy.
She changed the blanket for me to fit the season.
Oh, my.
(Tossing and turning)
He must be sleepy.
At 11pm, you'd fight with them about you staying or leaving.
Right. "I'm leaving."
- "No, it's late. It's dangerous." - That's right.
"It's not dangerous. I'm not a kid."
"Yes, you are."
Are you two writing a script?
- This is the repertoire. - It really is.
There are street lights everywhere even if I leave at night.
- The roads are well-paved too. - Of course.
"It's dangerous. It's too dark."
Of course it's dark. It's night.
- "Sleep over." - Driving is always dangerous.
I sleep over if I can.
Daegu is too far too.
- You should sleep over. - It's far. I should sleep over.
(Soon, he gets wrapped in comfort that his parent's place gives...)
(and sleeps soundly.)
Ki Bum.
(Getting up)
- Gosh, I passed out. - Come on out and eat.
- Indeed, moms are amazing. - Okay.
Come on out, Ki Bum.
(Let's eat, Son.)
That's the alarm. My mom's alarm.
I napped like I passed out.
You must be tired.
Your mom doesn't cook, though.
Did she buy them?
I napped like I passed out.
You must be tired.
Your mom doesn't cook, though.
Did she buy them?
It's been so long.
- You got a cake too? - Gosh, 34.
(Touched)
(Blowing)
(Happy birthday, son.)
Mom, it's been so long since we last did it.
I know.
I got you a gift too.
- Gosh. - Yes!
A gift from Mom and Dad.
We couldn't pick one as you're all grown up.
- Cash. - It's pocket money.
A letter from your dad.
Dad wrote me a letter?
- A letter from your dad? - Of course.
Your dad wrote a letter.
Gosh, this is amazing.
(Seeing you pull off such a difficult choreography...)
(in your early 20s, it got me worried about your joints.)
He always types it.
I almost asked him to release his font.
On my birthday, they'd always write a letter...
and withdraw new bills from the bank.
- Really? - For pocket money.
"Even if you make money, someone needs to take care of you."
- They'd always do this. - Yes.
There's a pleasure in the feel of cash.
He wrote it in Daejeon and dropped it by here.
- Really? - Yes.
My dad works in Daejeon.
(Checking)
- They gave you a lot. - That's a lot of money.
I think there's about 1,000 dollars.
- I'll use it well. - Okay.
Regardless of me making money,
it makes me happy.
That's right.
All right, I made the bone soup...
that you miss.
I made the bone soup that you miss.
To celebrate the holiday...
- You made it? - and your birthday.
Yes, I made it.
You know how hard it is to make bone soup, right?
(4 years ago, she made seaweed soup for him.)
It's too bland.
(His mom wasn't interested in cooking much...)
(because she was busy working.)
KEY cooks better than his mom.
I did my best to make it.
I got up at 4am for it.
It took five hours to drain the blood.
She must've gone through a lot.
(She got up early in the morning and worked hard.)
(She put in a lot of effort for a long time...)
(for his son who'd love the soup.)
You must have tripe in the bone soup.
Yes.
- Tripe? As in cow stomachs? - Yes.
Yes, tripe.
- Tripes are really hard to handle. - You're right.
There aren't many places that sell tripes because it's summer.
So I went to the butcher's in front of the slaughterhouse...
in Geumdan-dong.
(Surprised)
Oh, it's made with lamb?
No, the cow stomach.
- Oh, it's not made with lamb? - No.
Are you from Mongolia?
The cow stomach.
- Stomach? - His grandma isn't from Mongolia.
- The cow stomach is called tripe. - As in beef tripe.
- We call them beef tripe. - Oh, the thing...
I thought it was lamb.
There are many people who don't know that.
Many people don't get it either.
You know, like beef omasum.
Cows have four stomachs.
There are so many things to learn.
You made Grandma's soup?
- That's right. - I've really wanted to eat this.
They don't sell this anywhere.
They don't.
It's really hard to get tripes these days
Really? They're hard to get?
It's hard to get fresh tripes.
They have a gamey smell.
I was really surprised to see the beef bone soup.
It's really time-consuming.
It's my grandma's recipe.
Bone soup, braised crab in soy sauce.
It's braised crab in soy sauce.
- Crab soup. - There were a few dishes...
that I liked.
(Grandma's dishes that KEY used to love)
There are days...
when I don't crave anything.
But I always want that dish.
- Always. - There are dishes like that.
I always craved it ever since I was young.
I always liked it constantly.
(Grandma's bone soup that his mom made)
Try the soup first...
- Thank you for the food. - and see if it tastes the same.
(Carefully taking the first sip)
(We're curious.)
(Exclaiming)
- Gosh, it's good. - Does it have the same taste?
It's so good.
It was the same taste as the one Grandma made.
This is...
not the kind of soup you can have...
in just any bone soup restaurant.
It's a little different.
- The taste. - It's totally different.
It was so good.
I can tell how serious you were.
- I can tell from here. - It was so good.
- It's so good. - Right? I like it too.
I'm glad.
It was worth all the trouble seeing how you eat so well.
Your mom is really happy too.
I used to love tripes.
Yes, you did. You said you couldn't call it bone soup...
- if it didn't have tripes. - That's right.
- That's the one. - Oh, that?
That's right. That's the one.
Does it taste similar?
Yes! It's so good.
- It was exactly like this. - Yes.
(Thanks to his mom, he got to enjoy the taste he missed.)
It's good.
Ki Bum is eating so well.
I was worried that it wouldn't taste the same.
(Worried that it wouldn't taste like his grandma's dish)
If it tastes the same to you,
that means it'd taste the same to me too.
Still, you'd remember it the best.
Right, because I used to love it.
It's nice that it tastes the same.
I know.
I'm having this...
after around 13 years.
I still have the last batch that Grandma made.
What?
- You still do? - In the freezer.
Oh, you froze it.
I can't have it now.
You can't.
The last bone soup Grandma made before she passed...
is still in my freezer.
I couldn't eat it.
It's never been thawed for 13 years.
I always brought it with me whenever I moved.
You couldn't throw it away.
- I could never throw it out. - Of course not.
Give it to me. I can try it.
- That... - He's a frozen food expert.
Wait. I don't think he should eat that.
- I'll do a review on it. - Kian84, that's...
You'll get sick even if you're Elsa.
Let's have it on the field day.
- On the field day? - Seriously...
Make a whole pot of it on the field day.
It's a festival.
It's really precious, but if you actually eat it,
you might be able to see Ki Bum's grandma.
That's what we're worried about.
- "Hurry here." - We should say hello.
- You should. - "Hurry here."
- I'm good with the elderly. - Sure.
She probably knows that I couldn't eat it...
not even once after Grandma passed.
That's like my grandma's aged kimchi.
Also, I told her a few times in passing...
that I want to eat it,
but no restaurants have bone soups that taste like hers.
It was really good. I haven't felt that in a long time.
(Thanks to Mom, I could taste it again.)
Is it different from the regular bone soup?
As for my grandma,
she drains the blood for hours.
She throws out the soup she boils for the first time.
She throws out the second batch too.
So it's really time-consuming.
The ones with a lot of intestines...
- are usually spicy. - That's right.
- Because of the smell. - It's because of the smell.
She used really nice tripes,
which added a nutty flavor.
- The nutty flavor from meat. - The intestines...
The nutty flavor from the intestines...
- is added. - I wonder what that tastes like.
I want to try it.
(Gulping down)
- You need to drink that... - That's it.
Instead of using a spoon.
- It's like medicine. - It's like medicine.
(Grandma's bone soup is like tonic.)
Grandma must be happy.
(Yes, this hits the spot.)
It must be delicious.
Since you were at it,
you should've made this much like Grandma used to.
I did.
- You did? - I froze some.
You can take them.
Yes, there was a reason why she made a lot.
Didn't your moms...
feed you bone soup for a month...
once she made it?
- Of course. - She made a whole pot.
- They'd use a huge steaming pot. - I used to have it a lot.
- Right? - Before going to school,
- she added rice and fed me. - You had to finish it.
That's right.
She told me to have the soup, at least.
- Yes. That's right. - That's right.
- She'd tell us to drink it. - That's right.
I used to be really skinny.
After having that,
- Come on. - I gained weight.
- Don't be ridiculous. - No, when I was a baby.
Who's not skinny when they're a baby?
You seem to lie well.
Everyone was skinny when they were a baby.
I was skinny.
But they said having bone soup...
would give you an appetite.
- Since then, I have gained weight. - How many tons of it did you have?
Bone soup gave you an appetite.
I got an appetite when I was young.
You got a lot of appetite.
I did.
Try the radish kimchi.
I made this radish kimchi.
It's not store-bought?
No, I made this.
To have with the bone soup.
So this is the only thing from the department store?
No, I made this too.
All of it?
Mom can do this much.
Really?
It was the first time Mom made every dish.
Now that she has time.
She has more time on her hands.
I learned a special recipe.
Radishes like this aren't sweet.
So, you need to add this bit of MSG.
- Yes, you must. - You need to add it.
It looked like she was finding cooking fun.
You're right.
(Mom, you're the best. This is so good.)
Actually, to me,
it was the day I was born.
Just that, no more or less.
Just because something sad happened,
I didn't want to be too down.
I'd rather remind myself of the things I was grateful for.
It's a day for me to recharge and reset...
to move forward.
That's how my birthday would be.
I'm so happy that you're eating so well.
This is really...
It feels like I'm traveling through time.
It means so much to me.
- I'm full. - Seriously.
The strength that food gives you is really big.
(Next story)
(She's back here after a long time.)
(She takes a step...)
(and plops down.)
Gosh, this is so hard.
(The house she entered with much difficulty)
(Grandma, Grandpa, Na Rae is here.)
(After both of them passed, )
(the house became empty.)
(Na Rae made up her mind to clean up the house.)
(It tortured me the moment I opened the gate.)
(Na Rae)
(We're here!)
(Why are you crying by yourself?)
(Trust us.)
It won't be easy to pluck them out.
(A bunch of weeds)
(Lifting with no problem)
(Continuing to work without hesitation)
(Kian84 is the head farmhand.)
(Moorincess only makes so much noise.)
(Clank)
(Studying the room)
(It's okay. Let's have coffee.)
(Sworn brotherhood)
(Strengthening loyalty while washing each other's back)
(Gosh, this feels great.)
(Laughing with her friends, )
(the old feelings are washed away.)
(Back to Home Together with Sworn Brotherhood)
(An authority on the musical stage, Kai)
(Shall I become another version of myself?)
(He sets off with determination in his combat suit.)
(Opening)
(Another stage of mine where I'll pour out my passion)
(The professor's office is filled with his favorite things.)
(Professor mode, on)
(What's important is confidence in yourself.)
(Filled with confidence, )
(he delivers coffee?)
(I'm the youngest.)
(Have some coffee, my seniors.)
(Nerve-racking conference time for the professors)
(Yes...)
(Nodding automatically)
(What do you think about it?)
(I think it's great.)
(He goes to the canteen to regain strength.)
(Give me a lot, please.)
Thank you.
(Pork cutlet is perfect for the youngest.)
(Goodbye to the healthy meal for a while.)
(Inhaling like crazy)
(I, Who Was an Authority on Stage, )
(Am the Youngest in This World?)